Subtítulos oficiales de Itunes. Corregido por VitoSilans-- ¡Inglés!
¡Soy inglés!
Sabes que soy inglés. Son granaderos, amigo. Este es el fin. De ninguna manera
es una locura. ¡Abran
paso! ¡Fuera del camino!
Vamos, vamos, vamos.
Along the mole. All the way.
The ship's about to leave.
Where's the bloody air force?
The navy's requisitioned her.
They'll be back in an hour.
My dad wants to be ready before then.
They've told us to strip her
and load those life jackets.
Some men across the Channel,
at Dunkirk, need taking off.
Some men?
Check fuel, Fortis 1 and 2.
70 gallons.
68 gallons, Fortis Leader.
Stay down at 500 feet to leave fuel
for 40-minute fighting
time over Dunkirk.
Understood. Vector
128, angels point five.
And keep an eye on that gauge,
even when it gets lively.
Save enough to get back.
No French soldiers.
No French soldiers. No.
Subtítulos oficiales de Itunes.
Corregido por VitoSilans--